

Contact

Mobile:

061-330-9735

Email:

sanit.pongkw@gmail.com

Facebook:

facebook.com/art.sanit.freedomlove

GitHub:

github.com/sanitpongkeaw

Skills

- Node.js (express.js)
- React.js/Next.js
- Strapi
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- Javascript
- Typescript
- PHP
- Tailwind CSS
- Ant Design
- Git
- Docker

Education

Computer science.

2016 - 2020

Sanit Pongkaew

Summary

My name is Sanit Pongkaew. I am a graduate of Naresuan University with a major in Computer Science. I have been working as a Full-stack Developer for 3 years and am currently seeking opportunities that bring enjoyment to my work. I aim to work with new and exciting projects that not only keep me engaged but also allow me to develop my skills alongside the growth of your company.

Work Experience

PHP Programmer Trainee.

Igenco. | December 2019 - April 2020

Developed HR web application written in PHP

Freelance developer.

- Delivered 3 frontend web applications written React.js, Next.js
- bug-fixed features

Web Developer.

Temsol innovation. | October 2020 - March 2021

- Developed Travel plans web application written in Next.js, Node.js
- Developed Tour ticket management web application written in React.js, Node.js
- Developed the Temsol website to showcase information about the company and promote product sales written in PHP

Full-Stack Developer

Ookbee U (Thailand) Co.,Ltd. | December 2021 - December 2023

- Developed backend Fungjai application for artists to recommend written in Strapi
- Developed backend Fungjai application written in Node.js
- Developed web view for Fungjai application written in Next.js
- Developed mini-game web for use during Fungjai concerts, featuring games such as Bingo and Wordle. written in Next.js, Firebase
- Developed frontend responsive Mahorasop NFT web application for Mahorasop concert 2022 written in Next.js
- Developed Big data Fungjai concerts management web application written in FastAPI, Pandas, Next.js
- Developed Lensod web application written in Node.js, Next.js
- Developed Line chatbot for Lensod written in Node.js, Dialogflow
- Developed frontend Fungjai Academy web application using Shopify custom
- Developed Mahorasop web application written in Strapi, Next.js
- · Optimized, bug-fixed, and refactored code